...一篇重要的文章
...a substantial piece.
他们找到了一个女的
They found a woman.
她90年代中期的时候在游轮上工作
She was working the cruises back in the mid 90s.
翻译　水平有限的皮带断了
她说 莫叔叔要求与她
She says Uncle Mo asked for sex
字　　幕　　侠
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠
后期　Jason肖　特效　小布
和其他舞蹈演员发生性关系 这样才和她们续签合同
with her and the other dancers to get their contracts renewed.
ZIMUXIA.CN
校对　水平有限的皮带断了　时间轴　阿布
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
那 你还记得之前你让我销毁的
So you know when you had me destroy
压制　Jason肖
那些游轮的文件吗
those documents at Cruises?
监制　水平有限的皮带断了
好吧 我保留了一些
Well, I kept a few.
ZIMUXIA.CN
原 创 翻 译
中英双语字幕
那些文件 它们在哪里
Where are they, those papers?
我永远不会说的
I'll never tell.
我爸向我保证过 这不是个大问题
My dad has assured me that this is not a major issue.
我不想过分夸大其词 但是南有点打退堂鼓
I don't want to overdramatize, but Nan gets cold feet
你爸可能会失控
and your dad could lose control.
有时候 我觉得你需要的
Sometimes, I think you just need
只是宰杀一头好的过时的恐龙
a good old-fashioned dinosaur cull.
-你把他架起来活生生地烤  -别他妈惹我
- You barbecued him, live. - Don't fuck with me!
这事吹了
It's over.
拜托 冷静点
Come on. Calm down.
你13号和洛根谈过
You spoke to Logan on the 13th.
我希望你辞职
I would like your resignation.
我不喜欢被人欺骗
I don't appreciate being hustled.
什么他妈的 滚开 滚出去 滚远点
What the fuck?! Fuck off. Get out of here. Fuck off!
你不会正好有认识的药贩子吧
You don't have a connection for some powder, do you?
-有吗  -有的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
小心
Look out!
-不  -要
- No! - -Yes!
-不 不可能  -就要
- No, no fucking way! - Yes!
-不行  -什么 为什么不行
- No. - What? Why not?
我的意思是 你...你打算...
I mean, what, like, what... what...
你打算拿来干嘛
What are you even gonna do with it?
我要看看它 然后做个评估
I'm gonna look at it. And make an assessment.
不行 威尼斯怎么样
No. How's Venice?
肯德尔 我这不是请求 我这是强烈要求
Kendall, this is not a request; it's a demand.
我才不会把我的鸡鸡照片发给你呢 好吗 不行
I am not sending you a picture of my dick. Okay? No.
不行...你拿来干嘛
No... Why?
我要拿来做记录
I need it for my records.
我没办法说得很清楚 鸡鸡照片
I can't say this clearly enough. Dick pic!
-我听到了  -鸡鸡照片
- I hear you. - Dick pic!
鸡鸡照片 鸡鸡照片 鸡鸡照片
Dick pic! Dick pic! Dick pic!
好了 好了 去你的 行了啦 天啦
Okay, fine. Fine, fine, fuck you, fine. Jesus.
我操
Fuck.
你到底为什么要这样做啊
I mean, how do you even do this?
-那 怎么了  -没怎么啊 什么事都没有
- So, like, what was wrong? - Nothing. Nothing.
很好 一切都很好
It was great. It was great.
你为什么不先发给我看
Why didn't you send it to me before?
因为在"恐龙门"之后 我...
Just because after Dinosaur-gate, I just...
我想表明一个明确的态度
I wanted to get out a clear statement
-告诉他们我并没有牢骚满腹  -嗯
- and show them I'm not a sourpuss. - Yeah.
而且 你知道 我进入公司了
And y'know, I just, I got into it.
我想向他们展示 我有一个积极的计划 并且...
And I wanted to show 'em I have a positive plan, and...
他妈的
Fuck.
不 小西 我觉得 没经验...没经验是好事
No, Shiv. Like, raw... raw is good.
令人难忘 你知道吗 这就像...
It's memorable. Y'know, it's...
找到一个有收入 有活力的听众
Find an audience with an income and a pulse.
是的 那就是我的意思...我不是在对中心化说不
Yes, that's what I'm... I'm not saying no to the center
因为我...我是说关注广告收入
because I'm... I'm saying follow the ad revenue.
-嗯 是的 嗯 当然  -你能帮我拿着吗
- No, yeah. No, sure. - Can you hold this?
我认为里面蕴含的冷嘲热讽很明显
I think the cynicism was pretty clear.
你好吗 妹妹
What up, sis?
大型转储和流水线
Mega-dump and a line!
这简直就是...都是些...屁话
This is all... It's just... It's bullshit.
因为 实际上这就是...
Because what it is, really, it's just...
-是替换活动  -嗯
- It's displacement activity. - Yeah.
我只需要找到他 然后问他
I just need to find him and ask him,
"现在还是原计划吗 我还是接班人吗"
"Is it still happening? Is it still me?"
只是 你知道的 研究解决
Just, y'know, thrash it out.
你可不想研究 你想...你好
You don't wanna thrash. You wanna... There!
-嗨  -你好吗
- Hi! - How are you?
-彼得  -已经...
- Peter. - It's been...
已经很久不见了
It's been a long time.
听着 股东们想在股东大会之前
Look, the shareholders want a CEO successor named
任命一位总裁继任者
before the shareholder meeting.
他们已经说得很清楚了
They have made that clear.
所以 如果你真的把我们当做黄金搭档
So, if you're serious about us as a dream ticket,
等你成了大家关注的焦点 聪明的做法是能够先发制人
it'd be smart to be able to preempt any bad stuff
避免任何不好的事情爆出来
that could come out if you came under the spotlight.
好吧 好吧
Okay, okay.
好吧 你是想要我告诉你
Well, you want me to just tell you
我罗曼·罗伊做过的所有的可怕事情吗
all the terrible things that I, Roman Roy, have ever done?
如果我已经针对你做了一些反向调查 你会怎么想
How would you feel if I had some oppo research done?
看看社会最底层的顽强的人
See what a tenacious bottom-feeder
能挖出你什么料
could grub up on you?
我想这听起来很有趣
I'd say that sounds like fun.
我们去了布兰奇
We went Blanch.
谢谢你 格丽
Thank you, Gerri.
-谢谢你 格丽  -布兰奇
- Thank you, Gerri. - Blanch!
-为了内部调查吗  -布兰奇合作伙伴
- For the internal investigation? - Blanch and Partners.
漂亮的阿谀奉承的混蛋
Beautiful, soft-soaping fucks!
这次面谈会像
That interview is going to be like
-溜进泡泡浴一样轻松  -嗯
- slipping into a bubble bath. - Yeah.
我会在那儿点燃一支香薰蜡烛 放几首老鹰乐队的歌
I'll just light a scented candle in there, put some Eagles on
然后开始自己玩自己的
and start playing with myself.
他们来了 看看他们
They came. Look at them.
喂养槽里所有的小猪
All the little piggies at the trough.
所有关于游轮的流言 不过是一个他妈的什么都没有的汉堡
All the cruise noise, a fucking nothing burger.
他们现在仍然爱你吗 这点你放心吗
Reassured now that they still love you?
爱我 怕我 无所谓
Love. Fear. Whatever.
-我能和你说几句吗  -嗯 好的
- Could I have a word? - Yeah. Fine.
-爸爸  -等一下 小西
- Dad. - In a minute, Shiv.
我...对不起 但是我应该...你知道吗
I... I'm sorry but I should just... Y'know?
给我一分钟
In a minute.
你好
Hi.
-还好吗  -是的
- Okay? - Yeah.
兄弟 我要一个
Brother. I'll get one.
好的 1万8千块
Sure thing! That'll be 18,000 dollars.
你是否觉得自己被坑了一笔糟糕的投资
Ever feel like you're being fed a bad investment?
糟糕的投资
洛根·罗伊和他的家人们正在把一个曾经伟大的媒体品牌
Logan Roy and his family are taking a once-great media brand
韦斯达·罗伊科集团
连续10个季度 表现不佳
带入一条死路
down a dead end.
企业治理 失败
Corporate Governance. Fail!
企业治理
失败
收购策略 失败
Acquisition strategy. Fail!
接班人计划 失败
Succession planning. Fail!
罗伊家族正在辜负韦斯达集团
The Roys are failing Waystar.
作为股东 您现在就可以取代
As a shareholder, you can replace
作为股东
你可以行动起来
洛根·罗伊的橡皮图章董事会
Logan Roy's rubber-stamp board right now.
作为股东
你可以行动起来
投票 更换 董事会
投票表决 让今年的股东大会
Vote and let this year's shareholder meeting
投票 更换 董事会
为韦斯达集团 这个您拥有的公司
launch a fresh start for Waystar,
开创了一个新的起点
the company you own.
酷啊
Cool.
那 桑迪和斯图威已经发送了几千份视频出去
So Sandy and Stewy have sent out thousands of them.
发给了所有的主要股东
All major shareholders.
DF·金怎么说
What does DF King say?
他们说可能是时候开始担心了
They say it might be time to start getting worried.
是的 我们从几个主要投资者那里
Yeah, we've had some disappointing feedback
收到了一些令人失望的反馈
on a couple of key investors.
收购皮尔斯的计划在某些季度表现得很糟糕
The Pierce pursuit has played badly in some quarters.
杰克 那个"乌尔斯特人" 动摇了
Jack, the Ulsterman is wavering.
他有4%的股份 对吧 我们应该和他聊聊
He's four percent, isn't he? We should have a conversation.
和那个死肥猪聊吗 去他妈的狗日的
With that fat fuck? Fuck that guy.
你应该把你的鸡巴塞进他的肥动脉里
You should jam your dick in his one good artery.
还有一个人
There's also one other person
持有大量股票
who has a significant chunk of stock
我们听到风声说她也不再可靠
who we hear is no longer solid.
你母亲 卡洛琳
Your mother, Caroline.
真的吗 我妈
Really? Mom?
她有多少 3%的有投票权的股票吗
What is she, three percent voting stock?
我们一直指望着他们
We'd been kinda counting on them.
我的意思是 我们有36％的股权
I mean, we're at 36 percent.
如果没有他们的7% 那就很可怕了
Without their seven to add, that is scary.
我会和她谈谈 让她知道这事不是闹着玩的
I'll talk to her. Let her know this isn't funny,
她会因为错误的举动害死你
and that she can kill you with the wrong move.
嗯 我想 那正是吸引她的很大一部分原因
Well, I imagine that's quite a large part of the attraction.
我们认为 你去一趟英国亲自向杰克求助
We think that it'd be really helpful to get you to the UK
真的会很有帮助
for a personal appeal to Jack.
比如 明天
Like, tomorrow.
罗曼 肯德尔 和小西可以去说服他们的妈妈
Roman, Kendall, Shiv could hit their mom.
好的 伦敦 我去对付"乌尔斯特人"
Okay. London. I'll take care of the Ulsterman,
你们搞定你们的妈妈 但是要简单点
you're on your mom, but keep it simple.
小西别去
No Shiv.
我...对不起...等等 你是说 我们都去伦敦 你是这个意思吗
I'm... I'm sorry... Wait. You mean London, all of us, you mean?
你确定我们都要去吗
Are you sure we need to?
这就像...
That's like...
我们是什么 他妈的章鱼吗 四处延伸...
What are we? A fucking octopus? Giving, like, reach-arounds to...
捕捉礁石上的每条鱼 还是...
To every fish on the reef now or...?
好吧 放松点 色情鲈鱼男
All right, relax, branzino-porno-man.
没关系 没关系
It's fine. It's fine.
柯林会来的
Colin will come.
凯莉 我们可以搞定这事 对吧
Kerry, we can fix it, right?
你可以重新安排邓迪的事务吗
You can reshuffle the Dundee stuff?
关于新闻部门的事吗
About the journalism wing?
是的 我敢肯定他们会来找你的
Yeah, I'm sure they'll come to you.
然后直接去新加坡 基督城 就这样安排
Then straight to Singapore, Christchurch, do it that way.
我需要打几个电话
I need to make some calls.
凯莉 开始忙吧 弗兰克 格丽 我们开始吧
Kerry, we're hunkering. Frank, Gerri, let's get down to it.
这将是一个通宵
It's going to be an all-nighter.
-罗曼  -嗯
- Rome. - Yeah.
发生什么了 爸呢
What's happening? Where's Dad?
-我们有事要谈的  -呃...
- We're supposed to be talking. - Ye...
嗯 出了点事 他开始忙了
Yeah, yeah, something came in. He's hunkering.
他要我告诉你 "抱歉 改个期
He wanted me to tell you, "Sorry, rain check.
也许明天上午 也许" 你在咬牙切齿吗
Maybe in the a.m. Maybe." Are your nips hard?
肯定是 因为你被冷落得太厉害了
They must be, because you are so out in the cold.
继     承
第 二 季  第７集
-汤姆·万布斯甘斯  -是的 你好
- Tom Wambsgans. - Yeah. Hi.
感谢你抽出宝贵的时间
Thanks for making the time.
不 别客气 这事优先
No, not at all. Big priority.
不 我努力把我所有的爱抚都推到今天下午了
No, I managed to push all my gropes to this afternoon.
-我开玩笑呢  -嗯
- I'm just kidding. - Yeah.
这位是我的同事斯蒂芬·施特劳斯
This is my colleague, Stefan Strauss.
-嗨  -你好吗
- Hi. - How do you do?
-我叫肯尼斯·钱...  -嗨
- My name's Kenneth Chan... - Hi.
我们在"布兰奇合作伙伴"工作
And we're with Blanch and Partners.
嗯
Yes.
我们正在协助调查在"明亮星"游轮上发生的...
We are helping to investigate historic sexual abuse...
过往的性虐待事件
and associated wrongdoings
以及相关的不法行为
at Brightstar Cruises.
-好的  -所以 作为部门的负责人
- Sure. - So, as head of the division
-我们希望你能...  -好吧 简略地说 我 我...
- we were hoping you could... - Well, briefly, I, I...
我遵循比尔的长期管理 我只是一条
I followed Bill's long reign. I was but a minnow
尾随在...在比尔后面的小鱼
trailing in the wake of... of Bill,
他才是大抹香鲸 传奇人物
the big sperm whale, the legend.
当然 但是就你在公园部门任职期间而言 你是否知道
Sure, but in terms of your time at Parks, were you aware
过往有任何指控是以公司准则中
of any historical allegations that had been dealt with
规定的方式以外的途径来处理的
other than in a way outlined in the corporate guidelines?
简而言之 我不记得...
In my brief spell, I don't...
此时此刻 我不记得当时有任何事
at this time, recall anything that at that time,
引起过我任何真正的担忧
would have caused me any real concern.
好的 好吧 我们稍后可以对此进行深入探讨
Okay. Well, we can take a dig into that in a moment,
-但现在...  -当然
- but for now... - Sure.
在记录和文件保管方面...
In terms of records and document-keeping...
好吧 我们需要找到所有与这次调查有关的
Well, we need to locate all written information
书面信息
relevant to this investigation,
并保护这些信息不遭到破坏
and safeguard it from destruction,
忽视 或不正当处理
negligence, malfeasance.
你是否知道 有任何可能会
Are you aware of any document destruction
妨碍我们调查的文件被销毁
which might hinder our inquiries?
我...我想...
I... I think...
你知道吗 我...你知道吗 我只是...
You know what? I... You know what? I just...
我才意识到我们要在这里待上好一会儿
I've just realized we're gonna be here for a while,
我想全神贯注地配合你们
and I wanna give you my best attention,
但是我真的需要去上个洗手间
but I really need to pee.
我...我们希望你留在这里
W... We'd rather you stayed here.
我可怜的膀胱太弱了
I've got this pathetically weak bladder.
我就像一个莫名其妙生了个孩子的老太婆
I'm like an old woman who's had a baby somehow.
-所以 我要...  -嗯...
- So, I'm gonna... - Well...
但我...我很抱歉
But I'm... I'm so sorry.
我马上就回来 好吗
I'll be right back. Okay.
今天的飞行员是谁 不是瑟奇 对吧
Who's the pilot today? Not Serge, right?
-不是 先生 瑟奇停飞了  -很好
- No, sir. Serge is off rotation. - Good.
我喜欢无聊的闷蛋给我开飞机
I like a boring bastard flying me.
瑟奇经常看上去一副鸡鸡还没干的屌样
Serge always looks as if his dick's still wet,
他还准备给我起一个他妈的好的皮诺的名字
and he's gonna give me the name of a good fucking pinot.
你还好吗 儿子
Are you all right, son?
是的 我很好 谢谢你载我一程
Yeah, I'm good. Thanks for the ride.
很高兴见到你
It's good to see you.
我也很高兴见到你 爸 我希望我们可以一起说服老妈
Good to see you, too, Dad. I hope we can swing it with Mom.
是的 我...我本来想说
Yeah, I... I was gonna say,
你知道 西北风神大会发生的那件事...
you know, that thing up at Argestes...
不 嗯 那没...
No, yeah. . It's not...
我...我甚至都不知道你站在那里
I... I didn't even know you were there.
我的意思是 如果我知道的话 我会...知道吗
I mean, if I did, I would... Y'know?
我知道 嗯 我知道 当然
I know. Yeah, I know. Sure.
我有碰到你吗
Did I even make contact?
我觉得...没有...
I don't... think s...
嗯 我不太确定我们在说什么
Yeah, I'm not quite sure what we're talking about,
-老实说  -因为...
- to be honest. - Because...
我不会打你的 你知道吗
that's not something I'd do. Y'know?
是的 我知道 我知道的 我知道 我知道
Yeah, I know. I know that. I know. I know.
他妈的...
Fucking...
汽车 建筑物 到处都是
cars, buildings, everywhere.
他没有告诉你我要来吗
He didn't tell you I was coming?
没 没有 他没告诉我
No. No, he did not.
作为一个媒体人 他不是一个很好的沟通者
For a media guy, he's not the greatest communicator.
谢谢
Thank you.
总之 我正要去看戏 他问我
I was going anyway to check out some theater, and he asked
能不能和他讨论点事
would I talk through a couple things with him.
碰撞一点看法
Bounce some stuff.
-你觉得很"碰撞"吗  -老实说吗
- You feelin' bouncy? - Honestly?
有点泄气
A little deflated.
我做了那么多的幕后工作
After all the retreats I've done,
你知道 还是有点自负
you know, still got a bit of an ego.
嗨
Hi!
瑞亚
Rhea.
-爸爸 瑞亚在这里  -是的...
- Dad, Rhea's here. - Yeah, well...
别大惊小怪
Not a big deal.
当然不用大惊小怪 为什么会大惊小怪呢
Course it's not a big deal. Why would it be?
-这样很方便  -好的 我们开始吧
- It's convenient. - Okay, well, here we go.
罗伊男孩们巡回演出 我们全方位征服观众
Roy boys on tour, and we got 'em in all sizes.
阿尔法 贝塔 傻逼
Alpha, beta, cuck.
他妈的他要出国吗
He's fucking leaving the country?
而不是跟我谈话
Rather than speak to me.
你知道这事多久了
How long have you known this?
计划变了 所以...他想道歉
Plans change, so... He wanted to apologize.
胡扯
Bullshit.
你...
You...
小西
Shiv.
什么...
What...
-你知道他走了吗  -我能问你件事吗
- Do you know he's gone? - Can I ask you about something?
你能相信这事吗 他走了
Can you believe you this? He's gone.
他那群狗奴才甚至都没有告诉我
And his fucking flunkies didn't even tell me,
都帮着他隐瞒 我是不会接受的
running interference for him. I won't have it.
我不会像一个暗恋的女学生
I'm not gonna chase him around the party
在聚会上追着他的
like a schoolgirl with a crush.
不 绝对不行
No, absolutely.
我只是想确认一下 这事绝对是装装样子
I just wanted to check it definitely is bullshit
这个...这个内部调查
this... This internal investigation?
你知道吗 他甚至没有回复备忘录
Y'know, he hasn't even responded to the memo.
因为看上去并不像装装样子
Because that didn't feel all that bullshitty.
并不完全是垒球[闲扯]吗
It wasn't all softballs?
你曾经被垒球打过脸吗
You ever been hit in the face with a softball?
我的意思是 你参与这事有多深
I mean, just how inside this are you?
因为 不会把我拿出来垫背
'Cause there isn't a world, is there, in which I get
不会让我去送死
hung out to dry, in which I have to play the fuckbag?
-对吧 我的意思是...  -不
- Is there? I mean... - No.
他支持我 对吗 洛根
He supports me, right? Logan?
我的意思是 抛开笑话和嬉闹
I mean, never mind the jokes and the haha,
他不会拿我去送死 对吧
he's not gonna fry me, is he?
不 汤姆 不 我...你知道吗 我觉得我必须去那里
No, Tom. No. I... You know what? I think I have to go out there.
我必须...去解决这个问题 好吗
I have to... go and fix this, okay?
你还好吗
You okay?
当然
Sure.
当然 "当然" 不要惹大熊
Sure. "Sure." Don't poke the bear.
他可以秒杀一切 最好把他关起来
He can take anything. Load him up.
我他妈不知道
I don't fucking know.
所有这些能量 现在 每一次股东投票
All this energy. I'm gonna have to fight now
我他妈都要战斗
for every fucking shareholder vote.
我的前妻 我的老朋友都和我背道而驰
My ex-wife, my old friends turning.
我杀桑迪 桑迪杀我 那他妈的有什么意义
I kill Sandy. Sandy kills me. So fucking what?
下一个扎克混蛋来了
The next Zucker-fucker comes along
把你整个吞下
and swallows you whole.
像APP一样让你退出
Shits you out as an app.
是啊...
Yeah...
我们对潜在的下一任总裁进行了一些私人调查
We've had some private polling on potential next CEOs,
看谁会比较适合
who'd play well.
我很重视你的看法
I'd value your thoughts.
人选是你的子女吗
On the kids?
你觉得谁有资格
Who's got it?
我...我可以借助你清晰的视角
I... I could do with a clear eye.
作为参谋 好吧 那...
As execs, okay. Well...
小西自认为自己比实际上更聪明
Shiv thinks she's smarter than she is.
罗曼人实际上可能也不错 但是...
Roman could actually be good, but...
但是现在还远远达不到
but nowhere near right now.
肯德尔...我不知道
Kendall's... I don't know.
他就像被放在大尿布里一样
It's like you put him in a big diaper,
现在他可以随时随地拉屎
and now he can shit himself whenever he likes.
他拥有所有的机会
He has all the shots
但是他不知道什么时候用这些机会
but he doesn't know when to play them.
我...我不知道
I... I don't know.
哎呀
Yikes.
看看他们 他妈的在那嘀嘀咕咕的
Look at them. Fucking coochie-fucking-coo.
是啊 我已经有段时间没看到他这样了
Yeah, I haven't seen him like this for a while.
是的 自从萨莉·安妮和夏天骑马那次之后 就没有过
Yeah, not since Sally Anne and the summer of the horses.
-还记得那个狗家伙吗  -对
- Remember that shit? - Right.
-好吧...  -你觉得...
- Well... - Do you think...
你觉得他们在上床吗
like, do you think they're fucking?
天哪 你能想象吗
My God, could you imagine?
就像犀牛操蜂鸟
Like a rhino fucking a hummingbird.
她必须像女牛仔一样强悍 对吧
She'd have to go cowgirl, right?
不然的话 他很容易把她操断 就像根拐杖一样
Otherwise, he'd just like snap her like a candy cane.
伙计 你...是在...现在是在自言自语吗
Dude, are you... like... talking yourself hard right now?
儿子们 过来
Boys! Come on through.
过来 我猜 好吧 过来干嘛
Come through, I guess. All right. Come through what?
那... 小西的备忘录
So... Shiv's memo.
好吧 我们...我们...我们是要干嘛
Okay, we're... We're... we're what?
我们要把西沃恩的概念拿出来
We're putting the concept of Siobhan on the table
进行一般的讨论吗
for general discussion?
你要为了自己开心拆穿我妹妹的
You're tearing apart my sister's pious bullshit
那些尽责的屁话吗 我曾经做过这样的梦
for your entertainment? I had a dream like this once.
发表一些观点还是很好的
It's just good to air some views.
好的
Okay.
是的 我是说...我觉得...来自
Yeah, I mean, I think the... the twin quotes
托马斯·阿奎那和阿梅莉亚·埃尔哈特的引言真的...
from Thomas Aquinas and Amelia Earhart really...
砰的一声把我们踢开了
kick us off with a bang.
好多照片 所有那些微笑的孩子
So many pictures. All the smiling children,
所有的各种色调 ...连我这个顽固的种族主义者的
all the various hues, that... That melted the heart
心灵都被融化了
of even this hardened racist.
我...我喜欢这个行距......很宽
I... I like the spacing....Luxurious.
是的 但是内容呢
It is. But the protein.
好吧 可以肯定的是 不缺乏概念
Well, there's no shortage of concepts, for sure.
简直是一盆充满创意和流行词汇的秋葵汤
It's a rich gumbo of ideas and buzz words.
听着 我们应该温柔点 当你没有任何
Look, we should be gentle. It's easy to be overly critical
运营大企业的经验时 很容易就会
of the workings of a major corporation
过于挑剔企业的运作
when you have no experience running one.
我...你不能责怪她缺乏经验
I... You can't blame her for a lack of experience.
好吧 当然可以
Well, sure you can.
看着吧 换了是你 很快就会掌握窍门的
Just watch, you'll get the hang of it soon enough.
不用了 谢谢 但是那些真的很不错
No, thanks. But those are really good.
那些是有机的 我要抓住他看看有什么...
Those are organic. I'll grab him and see what's...
汤姆
Tom.
-格雷格 最近怎么样  -挺好的 不错 是啊
- Greg! How ya doin'? - Good, good. Yeah.
-伙计  -不错 是的 只是很忙
- Bud. - Good, yeah. Just busy.
只是...你为什么
Just... Why are you...
-当然 这是怎么回事  -我只有和几个
- Sure, what's going on? - I'm just have a few,
-和几个朋友共进晚餐  -看看你 花哨的家伙
- a few pals over for dinner. - Look at you, Fancy Dan.
成年人格雷格 你在说什么
The Greg Man. What are you talking about?
欢迎来到下一波
Welcome to the next wave.
只是一家翻新过的清谈俱乐部
Just a talking shop for renewal.
"只是一家翻新过的清谈俱乐部 "
"Just a talking shop for renewal."
不不不 很好 很好 我们没事
No, no, no. It's good. It's good. We're good.
听着 我想
Listen, I wanted to,
我想问你点事 我之前在附近
I wanted to ask you. I was in the area, actually,
所以我过来 我是想问你
that's why I came round. I wanted to ask you,
你今天和那些家伙谈得怎么样 面谈
how was today with the guys? The interview?
嗯....
Yeah....
嗯 好吧 我...有点紧张
Yeah. Okay, I... A little bit jittery.
压力减轻了一点
A bit of a stress comedown.
你知道 我理发了
You know, I, got a haircut.
即使我并不需要理发
Even though I didn't really need a haircut.
-对  -我想 我只是希望有个人
- Right. - I think I just wanted someone
摸摸我的头 让我舒缓一下
to touch my head, you know. Soothing.
而且 我觉得我有点压力...  -格雷格 格雷格
And, I guess I found it a little bit stressful... - Greg. Greg.
那 我想问这个 格雷格 你记得那些文件吗
So, here's my thing. Greg, you know the papers?
副本 我想要它们
The copies? I want them.
是的
Yeah.
我完成了交易中自己的那部分 你有了办公室
I did my part of the deal. You got the office,
里面有一张漂亮的古斯塔夫·克里姆特的小海报
a pretty little Gustav Klimt poster up there,
现在 是时候把文件拿给我做人身保护令了
and now it's time for me to habeas the corpus.
不 对 对 我...我...我的意思是 我只是想...
No, right, right. I... I... I mean, I just guess...
我...我只是想 它们就像我的保险单一样
I... I just guess that they're, like, my insurance policy.
是的 但是你不需要保险单
Yeah, but you don't need an insurance policy.
好吧 我是以防万一情况变得很糟糕
Well, in case things were to turn nasty.
情况不会变得很糟糕
They're not gonna turn nasty.
好吗 不会有人打断你的双腿 你知道吗
Okay? No one's gonna break your legs, y'know?
好吧 这听上去就有点糟糕
Okay, well that feels a bit nasty.
但是 正是你的保险造成了这种糟糕
But it's the insurance which is causing the nastiness.
如果你没有保险 你会更加安全 很讽刺吧
If you were uninsured, you'd be a lot safer. Ironically.
好吧 文件实际上不在这里
Okay, well, they're not actually here,
-所以我真的不知道该怎么跟你说  - 好的 格雷格 格雷格 听着
- so I don't really know what to tell you. - Okay. Greg. Greg, Greg. Look.
好吧 你的牌打得很好 我喜欢
Okay, you played your hand very well. I like it.
我真的喜欢
I do.
但是 我们现在必须结束这一切
But we need to end this now.
不然 我就告诉洛根 你已经复制了敏感文件
Or I tell Logan that you took copies of sensitive documents.
哦...好吧...
O... Okay, that...
好吧 我不...
Well, I don't...
好吧 我...我把文件放在...
Okay, well, I... I keep them at...
我把文件放在办公室里了
I keep them at the office.
你把文件放在办公室里了吗
You keep them at the office?
是啊 因为那些文件是工作
Yeah. 'Cause they're work.
我要去...我明天早点去
I'll go... I'll go in early,
明天早上第一件事就是把文件给你
and I'll give them to you first thing tomorrow.
对 对 但是...但是...但是...
Right. Right. But... But... But...
除了我信不过你
Except I can't trust you.
好吧 这不是针对你
Okay, it's not personal.
我就是信不过你 所以 以友好的方式
I just can't trust you. So, in a friendly way,
我今晚要住在这里
I'm staying here tonight,
我明天和你一起去公司
and I'm gonna travel in with you tomorrow,
我要和你一起去你放文件的地方
and I'm gonna go with you to wherever you have the papers,
-然后一起...  -伙计
- and then later, together... - Dude.
我们要在公司大楼以外的地方把它们销毁
We're gonna dispose of them off-premises.
而且 如果你尖叫或者试图复印
And if you squeal or you try to take copies,
我会打断你的腿
I'll break your legs.
抱歉 我希望你不介意在家里吃饭 但是 只是...
Sorry, I hope you didn't mind eating in. But it's just...
这个城里的狗仔队 都是他妈的禽兽
paps in this town, fucking animals.
当然 要是有人能对他们施加一些影响就好了
Sure. If only someone had some influence over them.
你还好吗
You okay?
西沃恩过来了
Siobhan's coming over.
很显然 她大发雷霆
Apparently, she's all fired up.
我想 你应该见过自己的孩子
I imagine you've seen a few temper tantrums
-大发脾气吧  -我不知道
- from your children. - I don't know.
她想要答案
She wants answers.
好的
Okay.
如果你说对了怎么办
What if you're right?
如果她没有自己以为的那么聪明怎么办
What if she doesn't have it in her?
我不是这么说的
That's not exactly what I said.
我担心她
I worry for her.
你知道吗 也许我步子迈得太大了
Y'know, maybe I jumped too fast.
不过 目前还没有公开宣布过 对吧
Nothing's been said publicly though, right?
对肯德尔来说 这不是最好的情况
With Kendall, it wasn't the best situation.
也许我应该说"管它的" 然后让她接手
Maybe I should just say "Fuck it" and let her do it.
我他妈也不知道
I don't fucking know.
她什么时候过来
When does she get in?
明天
Tomorrow.
你知道吗 如果你想让我...
You know, if you wanted me to...
我想我可以帮你解决这个问题
I think I might be able to help you make this go away.
很微妙地解决
It's delicate.
你想我试试吗
Would you like me to try?
让我看看我能做什么
Let me see what I can do.
你想留下来过夜还是怎么
You wanna stay over or what?
好吧... 我没想到会这样
Okay.... I wasn't expecting that.
好了 听着 根据对你的反向调查
Okay, so look. From the oppo research on you,
我要问你一些是与否的问题
I'm gonna ask you some yes-nos.
你的私教有没有在健身结束时
Did you get jerked off by your personal trainer
为你打过飞机
at the end of sessions?
不 不 我没有
Nope. No. No, I did not.
诽谤
Libel.
有传闻说 有个脸上有纹身的私教
There's rumors of a face tattoo situation.
不记得了 没有
No memory of that. No.
伙计
Dude.
你看到这个了吗 英国通讯社的
Have you seen this? From UK Comms?
什么
What?
凌辱致死
-格丽 你...  -什么
- Gerri, have you... - What?
凌辱致死
看到这个了吗 我再给你回电
Seen this? I'll call you back.
-爸在哪儿  -妈的
- Where's Dad? - Shit.
-他醒了吗  -我不知道
- Is he awake? - I don't know.
他是...自己一个人吗
Is he... like, on his own?
瑞亚回家了吗
Did Rhea go home?
我进来的时候他们在喝苏格兰威士忌
They were having Scotches when I came in.
我当时在梅菲尔区的爱德华地狱 你什么时候进来的
I was at Edward's hell hole in Mayfair. When did you get in?
你有没有带妞回来
Did you bring a piece of ass back with you?
-因为我感觉我听到声音了  -他得看看这个
- 'Cause I think I heard. - He needs to see this.
你觉得...我应该叫醒他吗
You think... Should I wake him?
我想是的 是的
I think so, yeah.
管它妈的 他得看看看这个 我去叫他起来
Fuck it, he needs to see this. I'm gonna get him up.
把他叫醒 当然
Wake him up. Definitely.
你会看到他正在操逼
You're gonna see him boning.
爸
Dad.
进去吧
Just go in.
他得看看这个故事
He needs to see the story.
-进去吧  -老弟 你滚蛋
- Go in. - Dude, fuck you.
好了 我要进来了 爸爸
Okay, I'm coming in, Dad.
爸
Dad.
我他妈的这是在哪
Where the fuck am I?
这个家庭的说法是情感上的痛苦
The family's line is emotional distress.
是的 他们说你打了他
Yes, they're saying you punched him,
实际上 这导致他将汽车驶进河里
which caused him, in effect, to drive his car into the river.
我没有打任何人
I did not punch anyone.
是的 这...这个说法不对
Yeah, this is... This is incorrect.
我从没碰过那个孩子
I never touched that kid.
好吧 我的意思是...吼过他
Well, I mean... shouted a little.
-推倒了一杯酒 但是...  -别嘀嘀咕咕的
- Jostled a glass but... - Stop mumbling!
最...最多吼过他
At... At most, you shouted.
-难道...  -我吼了他 所以他投河自尽吗
--Did... - I shouted him into the river?
不 我就是这个意思 我...
No, that's what I mean. I'm...
我是说这样的逻辑不对 这个...
I'm saying that it's not right. This...
我根本就不该来的
I should never have come.
我掉进了陷阱
I walked into a trap.
你们给了我很糟糕的建议 你们听到了吗 格丽  卡罗丽娜
I've been badly advised. You hear that, Gerri? Karolina?
-是的  -是的 我们听到了
- Yeah. - Yes, we heard.
雨果在那吗
Is Hugo there?
我觉得我们在法律责任方面
I don't think we have any huge concerns
没有任何大的担忧 对吗
in terms of legal liabilities, right?
他妈的 不是 不是 他们说你有注意的义务
Fuck no. No, they're saying you owed a duty of care
并且威胁要采取法律行动 不过 这行不通的
and threatening legal action, but that won't fly.
问题是 我们听说他们可能会来美国
The issue is we hear that they may come to the US,
并且带着这个故事上晨报
and appear on the Morning Juice with this,
-这样就不是...  -我听到的是
- which would not be... - From what I hear,
他们真正想要的只是道歉
what they really want is actually just the apology.
-个人道歉  -不
- A personal apology. - No.
当然
Sure.
我想唯一的问题是 就代理权之战而言...
I guess the only thing is, in terms of the proxy battle...
正是桑迪的小报把这事挑起来的
It's Sandy's tabloid that's stirring this up.
-他们去采访了他们  -当然
- They went and interviewed them. - Of course.
这显然是在吓唬我们的股东
It's a transparent effort to rattle our shareholders.
我们去拜访一下那家人 怎么样
How about we offer a visit to the family?
我们也许可以从他们那里得到一份声明
We may be able to get a statement out of them
为你开脱罪责
absolving you of guilt.
只是为这件事造成的所有的痛苦道个歉
Just say sorry, and for all the distress.
但我们明确指出 桑迪和斯图威
But we make it clear that Sandy and Stewy
用一个死去的孩子的鲜血做人血馒头
are beating their drum with the bones of a dead kid.
这样事情就会反弹
So it rebounds.
你觉得那样能让我脱困吗
You think that gets me out?
-当然可以  -是的
- Definitely. - Yes.
是啊
Yeah.
好吧 我想现在每个人
Well, I suppose everybody
都要为每件事道歉
has to apologize for everything nowadays.
好了 好了 安排吧
Okay. Okay. Set it up.
-好的  -会安排的
- Great. - Will do.
现在就安排
On it.
再见 各位 你昨晚过得开心吗 老爸
Bye, guys. You have a fun night, Dad?
-这话他妈什么意思  -没什么
- What the fuck does that mean? - Nothin'.
你好
Hi.
好的 好吧
Okay. All right.
爸 你还记得娜奥米·皮尔斯吗
Dad. You remember Naomi Pierce.
她在参加威尼斯双年展
She was in Venice at the Biennale,
所以 她很方便过来这里...
so, it was easy for her to pop over and...
意大利外卖哦 不错
Italian take out. Nice.
感谢你的邀请
Thanks for having me.
你堂姐好吗
How's your cousin?
实际上她这个月在休假
She actually is taking the month off
-去卑诗省旅游了  -肯定是
- to visit British Columbia. - I bet she is.
我觉得 整个这次的收购经历
I think the whole sale experience
-让她心力交瘁  -是的
- was quite draining for her. - Yeah.
我只能想象
I can only imagine.
娜奥米 向她转达我的问候
Naomi, send her my love
还有问候你们他妈的整个家族 好吗
and the whole fucking gang, won't you?
-儿子们 我需要几分钟谈谈策略 单独谈  -好的
- Boys, I need five on strategy in private. - Yep.
我...
I'll...
-一会见  -一会见
- Later. - I'll see you over there.
再见
Bye.
厉害
Nice.
那...关于你们的妈妈
So... on your mom.
有可能只是废话
Probably just bullshit.
她一直都是个老大难
She's always been a piece of work.
看看你们能不能甜言蜜语说服她 如果有必要
See if you can sweet talk her. And if necessary,
给她一个出价 让她重新站在我们这边
make her an offer that brings her back into line.
我需要她那3%的投票权
I need her three percent.
好吧 我们必须拿什么来收买她
Well, what do we have to play with?
好吧 现金很难 因为那样看起来像贿赂
Well, cash is difficult because it looks like a bribe,
-但是...  -所以...
- but... - So...
重新签订离婚协议 也许用这种方式
reopen the divorce settlement, maybe?
是啊
Yeah.
给她一千万 看看她会不会答应
Offer her ten million. See if she pipes down.
我最高可以涨到5千万 但是那样我不会高兴的
I'll go as high as 50, but I won't be happy.
兴奋啊 慢慢磨妈妈
Exciting. Grinding Mom down.
那...期待晚餐吗
So... looking forward to dinner?
嗯 我上次在那里吃饭的时候
Yeah, last time I ate there,
六个人吃三条泥泞的鳟鱼 里面塞满了芥末
it was three muddy trout for six and fill up on mustard.
可怜的混蛋
Poor bastards.
没得选啊
Slim pickings?
无论发生什么 我们都需要她的投票
Whatever happens, we need her vote.
-不惜一切代价  -不惜一切代价 对
- Whatever it takes. - Whatever it takes. Right.
好吧 爸 明白了
All right, Dad. Got it.
但是 我不喜欢被人玩弄 所以 把她拧干一点
But I don't like being fucked. So, screw her out a bit.
5千万以内你们节省下来的钱 我们可以拿来分了
Anything you save under the 50, we can split.
好吧 那应该包括...后续治疗费
Well, that oughta cover the... subsequent therapy.
-好 不 不 我在开玩笑  -嗯 我也是
- Yeah. No, no. I'm kiddin'. - Yep. Me, too.
-我们需要她  -明白了
- We need her. - Got it.
怎么 瑞亚留得很晚还是...你们...
What, did Rhea stay late or... Did you guys...
为什么问
Why?
没什么
Nothing.
不不不不 我的意思是...
No. No, no, no. I mean, just...
我...我只是想说...
I... I just wanted to say...
别误会我的意思
and don't take this the wrong way,
比如...
like...
你确定和瑞亚合作是个好主意吗
Are you sure this thing with Rhea is a good idea?
感...感觉...
It... It feels like...
是的 感觉她可能在玩你
Yeah, it feels like she could be playing you?
-我可以照顾好自己  -当然
- I can take care of myself. - Sure.
我...我知道你可以照顾好自己
I... I know you can take care of yourself,
而且你知道 你的事就是你的事 我只是...
and you know, your business is your business. I'm just...
你才是被女人打击过的人
You're the one who's cunt-struck.
好吧...不 我...我是...我只是...
Okay... No, I... I'm... I'm just...
只是看起来可能不太好
It's just maybe not a good look.
老家伙...不是...不是老傻瓜 但是 你知道...
The old f... Not... Not the old fool, but, y'know...
那...我不是这个意思
That... That's not what I'm saying.
我...我是说 她可能会让你看起来像那个样子
I'm... I'm saying that's how she could make you seem.
只是...说实话
Just... Just being honest.
我很欣赏
I appreciate it.
好吧...我想娜...娜奥米
Okay, well... I think Na... Naomi
想我带她去摄政动物园
wants me to take her to The Regent's Park Zoo.
显然 我们两个人正在热恋
Apparently, we're in a fucking Simon and Garfunkel song.
-所以 我要去妈妈家...  -我觉得我们应该
- So, I'll travel to Mom's... - I think we should do
来点头脑风暴
a bit of, brainstorming.
是啊
Yeah.
你愿意跟我一起去吗
Will you come with me?
-就...  -到那个男孩的家里去
- As in... - Down to the boy's family.
对
Right.
我的意思是...
I mean...
-是吗  -是的
- Yeah? - Yeah.
好的
Okay.
我们应该在这件事上团结一致
We should stick together on this.
你不同意吗
Don't you agree?
爸爸在这里吗
Is Dad here?
你想喝点饮料吗
Would you like a drink of some kind?
不 不用 谢谢
No, I'm fine. Thanks.
看看这是谁来了啊 亲爱的罗伊
What's poppin', Malala Roy?
爸呢
Where's Dad?
你在追逐飞龙吗
Were you chasing the dragon?
他神出鬼没 又一次这样
He is ghost. Again.
-这不是很酷吗  -去你妈的 他在哪里
- Isn't that cool? - For fuck's sake. Where is he?
他在见"乌尔斯特人" 是吗
He's seeing the Ulsterman, no?
问候死去的男孩的父母
Paying homage to a dead kid's parents.
他在赛马会上见到了"乌尔斯特人"
He's seeing the Ulsterman at the races.
真的非常喜欢你的小小备忘录
Really very much enjoyed your little me-mo.
什么鬼啊
What the fuck?
是的 是...
Yeah, it was...
非常引人注目 就像眼睛裂开了一样
very compelling. It was like eye crack.
那...那 爸爸看了吗
W... Well, has Dad read it?
他没有回复你吗
Has he not got back to you?
因为他昨天就看了 所以 他有很多时间回复你
'Cause he read it yesterday, so he has had a ton of time.
去你妈的
For fuck's sake.
是的 我们都看了 就像开小型圆桌会议一样
Yeah, we all read it. It was a little round table thing;
我 肯 爸爸 瑞亚
me, Ken, Dad, Rhea.
瑞亚 瑞亚在城里吗
Rhea? Rhea's in town?
你对自己要接管的公司
Do you know nothing of the company
一无所知吗
you're supposed to be taking over?
你知道的 韦斯达 韦斯达·罗伊科集团
Y'know, Waystar? Waystar Royco?
我们发表仇恨言论 经营游乐园
We do hate speech and roller coasters.
去你妈的
Fuck you.
好了
Okay.
好的
我把这些交给你之前
Before I hand these over,
可以...我可以提一个最终要求吗
could... could I actually make one final request?
里奥 我隔壁办公室的
Leo, my neighbor here,
他像卡通人物一样打喷嚏
he sneezes like a cartoon character,
所以 我在想 也许换个角落办公室...
so, I was thinking maybe a corner office...
别太过分 格雷戈里
Don't overplay your hand, Gregory.
快点
Come on.
-好吧...  -快点
- Okay, w... - Come on.
上面写着"机密" 格雷格
"Secret," Greg?
怎么了
Yeah?
但不是"最高机密" 有趣
But not "Top Secret." Interesting.
只是"机密" 这很聪明
Just "Secret," that's smart.
这样大家就知道
Just so people know, you know,
-这些都是机密  -是机密 是啊
- that these are secret. - They're secret. Yeah.
我不知道 因为有时候 看门人
I don't know, 'cause sometimes, the janitors,
他们会过来扔东西 然后...
they come and throw stuff out and...
但是你看 信封上实际写着"收据"
But look, the actual envelope says "Receipts."
但实际上它们不是收据
But they're not, in fact, receipts.
格雷格 你真是一个犯罪策划天才
Greg! You're a criminal mastermind.
哪个通晓多国语言的天才才能有机会
What polyglot genius could ever hope
破解你这无法破解的密码呢
to crack your impenetrable code?
-闭嘴   -天哪
- Shut up. - God.
-淡定  -不好意思
- Easy. - Sorry.
感谢你抽时间
Thanks for making time.
是的 嗯 你知道 日程计划里有一个
Yeah, well, you know, an unexpected, gap
意想不到的时间间隙
in the schedule.
那你呢 你正好在这里吗
And you what, you just happen to be here?
-看戏  -真不错
- Seeing some theater. - Lovely.
"看戏"
"See some theater."
你爸爸让我顺便搭飞机
And your dad offered me the ride.
而且 聊...聊聊天很好
And look, it's... It's good to chat.
因为他是...
Because he's...
他是一个非常...你的父亲是一个硬汉 我...
he's a very... Your dad's a tough guy. I...
被解雇让我很难过
I took it pretty hard getting fired.
当然 当然...
Yeah, sure. Sure, and...
你知道的 我们感谢你为我们所做的努力
you know, we appreciate what you tried to do for us.
但是他很好 他对我很好
But he's been kind. He's been kind to me.
人们不会谈论他的善良
People don't talk about his kindness.
是的 不 他们不会 没什么大不了的
Yeah, no they don't. Not a great deal.
听着 我很坦率
Look, I'm being very frank.
我希望这样没问题
I hope that's okay.
-是太过了还是不好  -嗯 不...
- Is it too much or bad? - Yeah... No...
谢谢
Thank you.
我觉得我们之间有联系 我喜欢你
I feel we have a connection and I like you.
我知道如何通过自己的方式
And I know what it's like to fight your way through
在我们的行业里奋斗 你知道吗
in our industry, you know?
是啊 不 当然 我...我很感谢
Yeah. No, sure, I... I appreciate it.
因为你一定很喜欢玛西娅
Because you must be fond of Marcia.
那...是的 我们关系不错
So... yeah, we have a, relationship.
是的 你知道 非常...
Yeah, you know, a very...
运作良好的关系
functioning relationship.
好吧 听着
Well, look,
是的 我不知道该说些什么 我就是喜欢你
yeah, I don't know what to say. I just like you
我...我...
and I... I...
你父亲是一个很有魅力的人
Your father's a very appealing man,
-我希望...  -不 很好
- and I hope... - No, it's fine.
这...不 和某人的老爸睡觉之前先打探一下 这样很好
It's... No, it's good to check before you fuck someone's dad.
我是说 是的 做你的尽职调查 你的文书工作
I mean, yeah. Do your due diligence, your paperwork.
我需要签一份授权协议书什么的吗...
Do I need to sign like a release form or...?
我觉得自己真是个白痴
I feel like a total idiot,
所以 恭喜你
so, congratulations.
-不 你不应该这样想 这...不  -不吗
- No, you shouldn't. It's... No. - No?
因为你的牌打得很准
'Cause you play your cards pretty close.
谁说我手里有牌
Who says I have cards?
但是你还好吗
But you're okay?
老实说 不好
Honestly, no.
我觉得自己就像一个被火烤过的 木头烧过的笨蛋
I feel like a flame-roasted, wood-fired dipshit.
是的 我做了一件我说过永远不会做的事 然后...
Yeah, I did the thing that I said I was never gonna do, and...
现在 我不知道 我不..我不知道
Now, I don't know. I don't... I don't know.
好吧 问题是 你碰巧
Well, the problem is it just so happens
非常聪明又有才华 西沃恩
you're very smart and talented, Siobhan.
谢谢
Thank you.
但是...我爸怎么想的
But... what does my dad think?
对吧
Right?
我成功地让自己陷入了这种境况
I've managed to get myself into this situation
"我爸在想什么"成了我他妈的整个世界
where "What does my dad think?" is my entire fucking universe.
好吧 我是说...也许...
Well, I mean... maybe...
也许吧 现在不是让他知道的时候 你懂吗
Maybe, isn't now the time to just let him know, you know?
你还是候选人
You have options.
好的 是的 但是我不能对他虚张声势
Okay, yeah, but I can't bluff him.
当然 但是...我碰巧知道有一家媒体运营
Sure, but... I happen to know there's a media operation
需要一个充满活力的新总裁
in need of a dynamic new CEO.
我碰巧知道南·皮尔斯对你有些好感
And I happen to know Nan Pierce has a certain regard for you.
而且我碰巧知道 她不会介意
And I happen to know she wouldn't mind
把一根他妈的锋利的棍子
putting a fucking sharp, burnt stick
插进你爸的巨人独眼里
in your dad's cyclops eye.
我去皮尔斯吗
Me at Pierce?
这永远不会发生 是吗
That's never gonna happen, is it?
我不知道
I don't know.
但是我可以用干净的手段提出这个方案
But I can get it floated with clean hands,
而且他们肯定会考虑的
and they'll consider it for sure.
那就全都有好处了 把这个位置收入囊中
Then it's all upside. Keep it in your back pocket,
拿它向你爸摊牌 甚至真的接下这个工作
lay it out to your dad, or even take the job.
这个...
Well...
让我想想
let me think about it.
谢谢
Thank you.
那...
And...
那 今晚...今晚干什么 爸
So, what are... Whatcha doin' tonight, Dad?
今晚吗 切尔滕纳姆
Tonight? Cheltenham.
-"乌尔斯特人"  -是的
- The Ulsterman. - Yeah.
看着他吃完他妈的一整匹马
Watch him eat a fucking horse.
然后 我不知道 我...你知道吗
Then, I don't know. I... You know,
我可能会和瑞亚共进晚餐
I might have dinner with Rhea.
嗯 好啊
Yeah. Great.
是的 她从没去过切尔滕纳姆
Yeah, she's never been to Cheltenham.
是的 很高兴去切尔滕纳姆
Yeah, well, it could be nice to see Cheltenham.
不好意思
Excuse me?
你有意见吗
You got a problem?
没有
No.
看看这个地方
Look at this place.
- 你好吗  -嗨 我是科林
- How you doin'? - Hi. I'm Colin.
-我是马克思 很高兴见到你  -他和你在一起吗
- Max. Pleasure. - He's with you?
-是的 就是那个  -嗯
- Yeah, he's the one. - Yeah.
那 都有些谁 妈妈 爸爸
So, what do we got? Mom? Dad?
男孩的叔叔也在这里
And the boy's uncle is here also.
这位是菲利普·克利夫 他会拍几张照片
This is Phillip Cleave. He'll take a few photographs.
我会整理一些新闻评论
I'll put together some press comments.-
实际上 肯
Actually, Ken.
不如你跟我一起进去
Why don't you come in with me?
你需要我...
You want me...
好吧 你知道 这看起来有点奇怪
Well, you know, it looks a little weird.
你知道 我一路把你带过来
You know, I bring you all this way,
然后你像拉布拉多犬一样坐在车里 进去吧
and you sit in the car like a Labrador. Come in.
保罗 安德鲁的叔叔
Paul, Andrew's uncle.
保罗 很高兴见到你 我是洛根·罗伊
Paul, pleased to meet you. Logan Roy.
这是我儿子肯德尔
And this is my son, Kendall.
你好 你好
Hi. Hello.
史蒂文和特蕾莎在休息室
Steven and Theresa are in the lounge
-欢迎你们进来  -你先请
- if you'd like to come in. - Please.
特蕾莎 史蒂文
Theresa. Steven.
你好 你好
Hi. Hello.
-史蒂文  -罗根·罗伊
- Steven. - Logan Roy.
请问你喝茶还是咖啡
Would like a tea or a coffee?
嗯 你真客气
Well, yeah, that's kind.
我不用了 谢谢 非常感谢你和我见面
I'm good. Thank you. Thank you so much for seeing me.
你知道 这是一场可怕的悲剧
You know, this has been a terrible tragedy.
当然
Of course.
抱歉 请坐
Sorry. Take a seat.
我在泡茶
I'm doing teas.
不 我不用了 谢谢 谢谢
No, not for me. Thank you. Thanks.
喝水吗
Water?
好的 谢谢你 好的 请给我点水
Yes. Actually, thank you. Yes, please.
你住在你妈妈家吗
You staying at your mother's?
嗯 是的
Yep. Yes, I am.
好了 我们走吧
Okay, let's go.
爸
Dad.
你觉得我也许应该对他们说点些什么吗
Do you think I should maybe say something to them?
不用
No.
可怜的混蛋
Poor bastards.
他们经历了葬礼 你知道吗
They've been through the ringer, you know?
天知道他们怎么应付的
Fuck knows how they cope.
他们真的很尴尬
They're embarrassed, really.
他们知道他是一个瘾君子
They knew he was a druggie.
没错 这就是生活
Yeah, that is life.
别忘了这一点 对吧
Don't forget it. Right?
你知道 没有什么好羞耻的 我们的业务
You know, there's nothing to be ashamed of. Our stuff.
我们给他们带来一点欢笑 提供一些像样的电视
We give them a bit of a laugh, some decent TV to watch,
一些不会对他们居高临下的新闻
news that doesn't talk down to them.
都是他妈的好人 他妈的好人
Good fucking people. Nice fucking folk.
你知道 爸不会高兴的
You know, Dad won't be pleased.
好吧 她要求我出席 所以...
Well, she demanded my attendance, so...
比爸更害怕妈妈 有意思
More scared of Mom than Dad? Interesting.
这是什么 战时食品博物馆吗
What is this? A museum of wartime food?
这是拿来展览的 对吧 这些都不能吃
This is for display, right? None of this edible.
我们上次来买了些什么
What did we buy last time we came?
一个苏格兰炸蛋 我以为是巨大的炸饭球
It was a Scotch egg that I thought was a huge arancini,
还有一些猪油
and some lard.
我要根香蕉好了
I'm just gonna get a banana.
吃香蕉不会食物中毒的
Can't get food poisoning from bananas.
难说哦
You'd be surprised.
你好
Hello?
嗨...嗨...嗨 我卷入了一起犯罪阴谋
Hi... hi... hi, I'm involved in a criminal conspiracy.
"真的吗" 是的 是的 我是
"Really?" Yes, yes, I am.
是的 我...我销毁了一些本不该拥有的文件
Yes, I... I destroyed some papers that I shouldn't have.
"是吗" 是的 我这样做了 那样很糟吗
"Did you?" Yes, I did. Is that bad?
"是的 那很糟糕 是的 那可能很糟糕
"Yeah, that's bad. Yeah, that could be bad.
你可能会坐牢 是的 你想要坐牢吗
You could go to jail. Yeah, would you like that?
你想那样吗 你这么帅气的小伙子
Would you like that, pretty boy like you?
你想那样吗
Would you like it?
你可能...你甚至可能会喜欢那样"
You might... You might even like that."
男性鸡奸 鸡奸男性
Male rape. Rape of the male.
那是夹克下面的口袋
That was lower jacket pocket.
夹克下面的口袋
Lower jacket pocket.
这是内袋 全部放在内袋里
This is inside pocket. All aboard inside pocket.
这是内袋 这是内袋
This is inside pocket. This is inside pocket.
我在这里 我在移动 我在走动 我在走动
Here I am, I'm moving. I'm moving. I'm moving.
轻快的运动 轻快的运动
Brisk movement. Brisk movement.
这样快了点 好吧 风在吹
This is faster. Okay, wind is blowing.
我在大声说话
And I'm talking louder.
"不 我不记得了 格雷格 不 我不记得了" 好的
"No, I don't remember, Greg. No, I don't remember." Okay.
犯罪阴谋
Criminal conspiracy.
"真的吗"
"Really?"
谢谢你 先生
Thank you, sir.
妈妈
Mom?
你好
Hello!
-嗨 你好  -西沃恩
- Hi. Hello. - Siobhan.
小罗
Ro-Ro!
妈妈
Mommy!
谢谢你们的光临
Thank you for coming down.
嗯 只是听命令行事而已
Yeah, well, just following orders.
像纳粹一样
Like a Nazi.
没错 对吧
Exactly. Right?
好吧 你门现在在乡下 所以你们打算做点什么
Well, you're in the country, so what were you going to do?
去苏荷区嫖妓吗
Go out whoring in Soho?
嗯 那会是第一选择
Yeah, that would have been the first choice.
好吧 听着 很显然 肯德尔去酒吧了
Well, look, Kendall's gone to the pub apparently,
所以 我刚刚做了一点鸽子肉
so, I've just had a little bit of pigeon done.
我觉得你们不会有谁感到非常饥饿
Didn't think anyone would be feeling terribly hungry.
我知道我不饿
I know I'm not.
不饿 是的
No, right.
-不想要大块的...  -当然不饿
- Don't want a great... - Course not.
圆面包
Bolus of gubbins.
-拿个盘子  -谢谢
- Take a plate. - Thank you.
接住
Catch.
那 你好吗
So, how are you?
好吧 如果你要研究这种问题
Well, I might just as well ask you
我也会问你这些问题的
if you're going to go into all that.
这...
It was...
这个问题又不咄咄逼人 妈妈
Wasn't intended as an aggressive question, Mom.
-这是...  -不 我很好
- It's... - No, I'm fine.
罗里很棒
Rory's wonderful.
那我应该做妈妈吗
So, should I be mother?
嗯 你干嘛不试试呢
Yeah, why don't you give it a go?
是的 很抱歉 这不是48盎司的T骨牛排
Yes, well, I'm sorry it's not a 48-ounce T-bone steak
配松露薯条 不过 请吃吧
with truffle fries, but there we go.
我可不希望冠心病发作
Some of us don't want coronary heart attacks.
这菜很好 妈妈 这很好
It's nice, Mom. It's nice.
鸽子里有很多子弹
There's quite a lot of shot in the pigeon,
所以 吃的时候注意下 不然牙齿要崩裂
so mind how you go or you'll crack a tooth.
子弹还可能会带进去一些羽毛
And the shot can take a bit of feather in, too.
子弹和羽毛
Shot and feather.
我们可以马上开始谈判吗
Shall we begin with the negotiation straight away?
十年来我第一次让你在家里过夜
The first time I've had you in for the night in a decade.
真是太丢脸了 这样你才可以帮着你爸
It's just a shame it's so you can put the squeeze on me
-挤压我  -妈 不是那样的
- for your father. - Ma, it's not like that.
-不是吗  -不是
- No? - No.
告诉我 被送到这里来
Tell me, what does it feel like
哄你妈妈 感觉如何
being sent here to wheedle out your mother.
不要看我
Don't look at me.
我又没有参与 她说的没错
I'm not getting involved. She's right.
谢谢
Thank you.
谢谢你 展现了一点点团结
Thank you, a bit of solidarity.
虽然晚了二十年 不过没关系
Twenty years too late, but never mind.
有人站在了妈妈一边
Someone's taking Mommy's side.
如果...如果你想站在我们这边 现在这样只是在装样子 对吗
If... If you want to get into it, you're just posturing, right?
如果你选择桑迪和斯图威
And if you go with Sandy and Stewy,
那你就会烧毁体育馆 而你自己的孩子也身在其中
you're burning down the Coliseum with your children inside it.
我已经考虑过了 我已经和罗里讨论过了
I've thought about it. I've discussed with Rory.
是的 很好 很高兴有他帮着出主意
Yeah, well, great to get his brain on it.
土豆
Potatoes.
他实际上很聪明
He's actually rather clever.
是的 他卷他的
Yeah, before he rolls
烟草和大麻烟之前还是有点脑子的
one of his tobacco and hash monstrosities.
-天哪  -对不起 你说什么
- My God. - Sorry, what was that?
没事 妈妈 有个金额
Nothing, Mum. There's a number.
开始了 开始凿心了 这样很好
Here we go. The chiseling begins. This'll be good.
我们可以从亲爱的老母亲那里抠走多少钱呢
How much can we screw out of our dear old mother?
好吧 爸爸 当然 这事和投票关系
Well, Dad, unrelated to the vote of course,
愿意重新商定离婚协议
is willing to reopen the divorce settlement.
那 多少金额
So, what's the number?
好吧 你想要什么
Well, what do you want?
我想惹怒你父亲
I want to piss off your father.
好吧 我觉得行得通
Well, I think that's working.
来吧 随便吃点吧 好了 开动吧
Come on, help yourselves. All right then, come on.
他的最高出价是多少
What's his top number?
好吧 他让我告诉你是1千万 但实际是4千万
Well, he told me to tell you ten, but it's 40.
-那就是5千万  -不 ...不 是4千万
- So, it's 50. - N... No, it's 40.
罗曼 你不擅长这种事
Roman, you're not very good at this.
不 真正的最高价是多少
No, what's the real top?
他没有真正的最高价
He doesn't have the real top.
爸爸永远不会告诉他的
Dad would never tell him.
我知道我想要什么了
I know what I'd like.
告诉他 我要夏宫
Tell him the summer palace.
汉普顿庄园
The Hamptons House.
你讨厌那里
You hate it out there.
是的 但是他喜欢那里 不是吗
Yeah, but he loves it, doesn't he?
他喜欢在那里开派对 和鄙视他的人
He loves the parties, the clam bakes
一起烤蛤蜊 非常多的乐趣
with people who despise him. Such fun.
但那里价值...值多少
But that's like... What is that?
差不多1.5亿了吧
That's like 150 million.
没关系 罗曼 这只是数字
It doesn't matter, Roman. It's just numbers.
我也会和"乌尔斯特人"杰克谈一谈
I'll have a word with Jack the Ulsterman, too.
可以把这加进去
Can throw that in.
-好的 但是...  -或者...
- Okay. But... - Or...
给我两千万...
How about 20 million...
你们这些孩子每年都陪我过圣诞节
and you kids give me Christmas every year.
来吧 妈 不带这样的...
Come on. Mom, don't make it like...
我很乐意来过圣诞节
I would like to come for Christmas.
当然
Sure.
不...是你从不邀请我们
No... You never invite us.
好吧 那是因为你已经说的很清楚了
Well, that's because you've made it quite clear
-你不会来  -那只是某一次
- you wouldn't come. - That was one time.
那是好几次
That was several times.
-我当时才18岁  -听着
- I was 18. - Look.
我想你圣诞节和我一起过...
I would like to see you for Christmas...
而不是总是和你父亲在一起
instead of you always being with your father.
你为什么不问问他想怎么选呢
Why don't you ask him what he'd rather?
他可以留着夏宫
He can keep the summer palace
如果我每年圣诞节都能有你们陪
if I get the family every Christmas.
离婚以后 你必须保持良好的
You have to have good lines of communication
沟通渠道 这绝对很关键
after a divorce. It's absolutely key.
所以 我觉得我们必须听听他更喜欢哪一个
So, I think we have to hear which he'd prefer.
让他来作选择
Let's make him choose.
你知道吗 你没来吃晚饭真是太可惜了
Y'know, it's a shame you didn't make it to supper.
结果是个相当不错的夜晚
It ended up being rather a nice evening.
对不起 我错过了
I'm sorry I missed it.
原来你父亲为了保留一块地产[夏宫]
Turned out your father was prepared to sell you all off
准备把你们像动产一样都卖了
like chattels to keep a piece of real estate,
不过 这一点也不让我感到惊讶
but that doesn't surprise me.
我就当你接受过来陪我过圣诞节的条件了
You're gonna be okay to come for Christmas, I take it?
好的
Great.
妈妈 妈妈
Mom. Mom.
我...我...
I... I...
有一些...有一些事我想...
have some... some things I'd like to...
谈谈 想...想告诉你
to talk about. To... To tell you.
不要再对我的情感缺陷长篇大论了
No more long lists of my emotional deficiencies.
不是的 妈妈
No, Mom.
不 这是...
No, it's...
是我做过的一件事...
It's something I've done...
让我感觉不太好
that I don't feel great about.
是吧
Right.
这样啊
Oh, Dear.
你觉得我们可以谈谈吗
Do you think maybe we can talk?
当然 肯定啊
Sure. Absolutely.
说吧 但是...
Go ahead, but...
哦 但是 是很困难的事情吗 因为...
Yeah, but are they quite difficult things? Because...
你知道的...我对令人不愉快的真相有点厌倦
you know... a bit tired for home truths.
对
Right.
好吧 是的 是有点困难
Well, yeah, it's a bit difficult.
好的.
Okay..
好吧...继续说吧
Well... go on.
-没关系  -不 不 我想听 说吧
- It's fine. - No, no. I want to. Come on.
-没关系  -不
- It's okay. - No.
如果你愿意 我们现在绝对可以谈谈 但是...
If you want, we can absolutely do it now, but...
你知道吗 也许吃个鸡蛋再谈会更好
you know, it might be better to do it over an egg?
当然
Sure.
我们...我们吃个鸡蛋再谈
Let's... Let's do it over an egg.
是啊 我们早上会感觉好一些
Yeah. We'll feel better in the morning,
我们可以明天再谈
and we can do it tomorrow.
好吧
Okay.
睡个好觉 亲爱的儿子
Sleep tight, sweet boy.
他妈的
Fuck.
伙...嗯 这 ...这事怎么会发展成这样
Du... Yeah, h... how did it come to this?
-这事怎么会发展成这样  -你说得对
- How did it come to this? - You're right.
-怎么了...  -你说得对
- What's th... - You're right.
没有人会知道
No one will ever know.
没有人会知道你派我来粉碎这些
No one will ever know you sent me to shred the records
账外黑钱和非法恐吓的记录
of off-book hush-money and illegal intimidation.
是啊
Yeah.
涂上消失的酱汁
Put on the disappearing sauce.
调味 调味
Sauce it. Sauce it.
好了 来一点净化的火焰
Okay. A little purifying flame.
-好了 退后一步  -好的
- Okay, stand back. - Yeah.
好吧 等一下
Okay, just a minute.
证据不希望被销毁
The evidence does not want to be destroyed.
操...
F...
"渎职之主 请赐予我们你神圣的祝福"
"Lord of Malfeasance, give us your divine blessing."
-帮我拿着啤酒  -好的
- Hold my beer? - Yep.
-好了  -这下好了
- Yeah. - Good!
-嗨 你好  -嗨...
- Hi, there. - Hi...
我来这里见洛根·罗伊
I'm here to see Logan Roy.
当然 这位先生会带你去见他
Sure, this gentleman will show you to him.
爸
Dad.
西沃恩....他们告诉我 你在这里
Siobhan.... They told me you were here.
真是意外
This is unexpected.
是啊 我们本来应该谈谈备忘录的
Yeah, we were due a check-in with the memo.
然后你从美国逃跑了 又从伦敦逃跑了
And then you fled the country, then you fled London.
-好吧...  -所以...
- Well... - So...
我的日程是凯莉在安排 我们出了一些紧急情况
My schedule goes through Kerry. We've had some emergencies.
是的 你有点神出鬼没 爸
Yeah, you're kind of elusive, Dad.
你为什么不告诉我你要来
Why didn't you tell me you were coming?
好吧 因为...
Well, because...
老实说 我担心你会再次逃跑
honestly, I was afraid that you would run away again.
我这辈子从没因为任何事情逃跑
I have never run away from anything in my life.
我们能不能...只谈谈备忘录的事
Can we just... just talk about the memo?
我欠你一个回应
I owe you a response.
你还没有...你还没看吗
You've not... You've not read it?
西沃恩 我有一个阿根廷那么大的收文篮[事务繁忙]
Siobhan, I have an in-tray the size of Argentina.
好的
Okay.
你知道...实际上 你知道吗 我还是...
You know... Actually, you know what? Also, I...
我还是要问 还是我吗
I need to ask. Is it still me?
什么
What?
拜托 爸
Come on! Dad.
是什么变了吗 因为 你知道 感觉就像是发生了什么变化
Has anything changed? Because, you know, it feels like it has.
而且 你知道吗 你当时说的时候...
And, you know, when you said it...
感觉真的很真实
it felt really real.
而且我知道...我知道你并不总是喜欢我说的话
And I know... I know you haven't always liked my words.
你对我说的话并不总是很满意
You haven't always been happy with my words,
但是拜托 我们可以讨论的
but come on. We can discuss.
你知道我想要这个位置 而且我可以做到
You know that I want this, and that I can do it.
那你为什么要耍我
Then why are you fucking me about?
哪方面...
As in...
争取皮尔斯的新总裁的职位
Putting your name in for the Pierce job?
-我...  -和那些背后暗算我的人谈话
- I... - Talking to those backstabbers.
那是什么意思
What's that all about?
如果你打算来这里
If you're gonna be coming in here
跟你父亲讲一堆废话 为什么还要那样做
talking a whole load of crap to your father?
-谁...谁告诉你的  -谁告诉我的
- Who t... who told you? - Who told me?
城里都传遍了
It's all over town.
南·皮尔斯在城里大肆宣扬 就像得到了战利品一样
Nan Pierce is shouting it like a war trophy in the city.
好吧 你知道吗
Okay, well, you know what?
我不得不保持选择的态度 爸爸
I had to keep my options open, Dad.
是啊 我懂了 我懂了 因为我们...
Yeah. I see. I see. 'Cause we...
因为我们有一些余波什么的吗
'Cause we have a little fallout or something?
我们是一家人
We're a family.
我们可能会有矛盾 我完全没想到你会这样做
We can have our bumps. I don't expect that.
-好吧 我不是我...  -家人 西沃恩
- Well, it's not that I was... - Family, Siobhan!
如果你不明白家人的意义...
If you don't understand that...
那就滚远点
then fuck off.
鸡蛋饼吗 她在做鸡蛋饼吗
Eggy pegs? She doin' eggy pegs?
她是...
She's...
如果她一会错过我们的离开 她为此道歉
She's sorry if she misses our departure.
她有很多事要做
She's got quite a lot to do.
当然 有可能发生
Sure. Can happen.
是啊 是的 有可能 对
Yeah. Yeah, it can. Right.
拿着
There you go.
爸 爸
Dad. Dad.
只是需要确认点事情
Just need to confirm something.
交易划算 对吧  2千万加圣诞节
Decent deal. Right? 20 and Christmas.
好孩子 好孩子
Good kid. Good kid.
是的 为了你 我把妈妈给耍了 你知道吗
Yep, I screwed Mom for you. That's, you know,
这事跟做梦一样 对吧
the fucking dream, right?
你现在应该去把你的眼睛挖出来 看是不是真的在做梦
You should probably go and poke your eyes out now.
对 是啊
Right. Yeah.
-小西怎么样  -我们吵架了 是啊
- How'd it go with Shiv? - We had it out. Yeah.
现在有了弹药
With the ammunition,
我想我脖子上的绞索掉下来了
I think I got the noose from around my neck.
-很好 很好  -谢谢
- Good. Good. - Thank you.
我很乐意帮忙
I'm pleased to help.
你知道吗 我一直在想...
You know, I've been thinking...
也许...也许在更宽的范围内寻找我的接班人
maybe... maybe look farther afield for the next me.
也许拟一份两三个人的候选名单
Maybe a shortlist of two or three?
我很乐意帮你找
I'd be pleased to help you look.
-嗯  -肯
- Yeah. - Ken.
听着 她在飞机上吗
Listen, is she on the plane?
好的 只是...我觉得我们有麻烦了
Okay, just... I think we've got a problem.
千万小心 好吗 我想我被耍了
Just be careful, okay? I think I got fucked.
ZIMUXIA.CN
关注新浪微博
@FIX字幕侠